bookmasters.com 2014-11-05

# Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

**Use and Protection of Personal Information**  
Bookmasters is committed to protecting your privacy. We will collect or record basic personal information (e.g., name, email address, mailing address, phone number) you voluntarily provide through our web site or through electronic mail you send to us, but we will not disclose this information to third parties. We also may ask you questions about your buying habits for particular product segments, or ask you to state the total dollar volume spent on a particular product. If you are inquiring about employment at Bookmasters, we also will ask for your Social Security number, your educational level, and your desired salary range. We will not otherwise collect or record any of your personally identifiable information, except as detailed below in the “Safe Harbor” section. Bookmasters will not disclose your basic personal information to third parties except when the release of such information is necessary to comply with law or to protect the rights, property or safety of our website. Bookmasters does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining prior, verifiable parental consent.

Your browser software contains a standard feature called a “cookie” which Bookmasters may use to enhance your experience with the website. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the website, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. Our site may also use graphic files known as “transparent GIFs” to count users who visit our site, as well as to open our HTML-formatted e-mail messages. If you have any questions regarding this statement, please contact us via phone at , or send us an email addressed to [info@bookmasters.com](mailto:info@bookmasters.com).

**Email Privacy Policy**  
The information we collect is used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve the content and services of our Web site and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers (no individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent), to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site and services, to send visitors our opt-in email newsletter(s) (if requested by the visitor), to provide users with the products and/or services for which they signed-up or registered which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via email, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without the visitor’s consent. If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [abuse@bookmasters.com](mailto:info@bookmasters.com) for review.

**Trademarks and Intellectual Property**  
AtlasBooks is a registered trademark of Bookmasters. All other product and service marks on this site are the trademarks of their respective owners. Moreover, all comments, suggestions, or other information sent to this site will become the property of Bookmasters.

**Safe Harbor**  
Bookmasters recognizes that the European Union (“EU”) has an “omnibus” data protection regime established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC) (the “Directive”). Among other things, the Directive generally restricts the transfer of EU Personal Information to Bookmasters operations in the United States, unless there is “adequate protection” for such Personal Information when it is received in the United States.

In order to address this requirement, Bookmasters adheres to the US-EU Safe Harbor Privacy Principles published by the US Department of Commerce (“Safe Harbor”) with respect to certain individually identifiable information about individuals in the European Union who are customers or employees of Bookmasters customers (“EU Customer Data”) and about individuals in the European Union who are Bookmasters or its affiliates’ employees (“EU Employee Data”) (collectively, EU Customer Data and Employee Data is referred to as “EU Personal Information”). Bookmasters practices concerning EU Employee Data is published to affected EU employees through other company policies and procedures. For more information about the Safe Harbor, please refer to the US Department of Commerce website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

With respect to EU Customer Data, Bookmasters operates as a mere data processor for its customers located in the EU, and its customers remain the data controllers with respect to such information. Bookmasters therefore acts in accordance with the instructions of such customers regarding the collection, processing and transfer of EU Customer Data, the provision of access to and rectification of EU Customer Data, and other matters. Bookmasters also maintains reasonable security measures to safeguard EU Customer Data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction and maintains reasonable procedures to help ensure that such data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted at the “Privacy Policy and Legal Notices” link on the site’s home page. In the event that the change is significant or material, we will notify you of such a change by revising the link on the home page to read “Newly Revised Privacy Policy.” Please check the Privacy Policy frequently. Your continued use of the site constitutes acceptance of such changes in the Privacy Policy, except where further steps are required by applicable law. This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 15, 2007.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about Bookmasters’ Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us at

Privacy at Bookmasters  
30 Amberwood Parkway  
PO Box 388  
Ashland, OH 44805, USA  
or e-mail us at info@bookmasters.com.
